danwei.org 2010-06-24

# Danwei | Privacy Statement

## Danwei Privacy Policy

Danwei collects certain information about our users. The type of data we collect and the ways in which we use it are explained below.

All user-submitted information and automatically-generated log files are hosted on a server in Hong Kong.

### Use of personal data

Danwei collects demographic information from our users through periodic surveys and when users sign up for Danwei services. This data is provided voluntarily by users and enables us to improve our website and services. No personally-identifiable information will be shared with any third party.

### Email contact from Danwei.org

Danwei may contact you:

  * in relation to Danwei services you have signed up for. Use of Danwei services is voluntary and can be canceled at any time;
  * if you have signed up to receive newsletters or notifications. You can always remove your contact info from our database if you no longer desire to receive these messages, or if your name has been added to our lists in error;
  * in relation to any comment you have posted on the Danwei website. Such contact may include but is not limited to: requesting further clarification, explaining why your comment was not published, and asking permission to edit;
  * in response to email sent to Danwei addresses.

Danwei will not reveal your name or contact info to any third party.

### Cookies policy

Danwei uses cookies to save user preferences. Cookies set by Danwei are not accessible by any other website. You may choose to adjust your browser settings to reject or screen cookies, but doing so may limit some features of Danwei.

### Logs

When you visit Danwei, our server automatically collects certain information, including IP address, browser type and language, and referring page. This information is tracked in aggregate form to allow us to improve and update Danwei. No personally-identifiable information will be shared with any third party.

### Third-party tracking

Advertising and other third-party content that appears on Danwei webpages but is not hosted on the Danwei server may set cookies to track user information. Danwei has no access to this data. Users should review the privacy policies of those third parties for further information.

### Changes to Danwei's privacy policy

This privacy policy may be updated from time to time. The current version can always be found at <http://www.danwei.org/privacy> and will bear the date of the most recent revision. This edition was revised on 22 October, 2007.

* * *

If you have any questions regarding Danwei's privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.danwei.org/editorial/about_danwei.php).
